export const quizzes = [
    [
        {
            'question': '2 + 3',
            'answer': 5,
            'penalty': 4
        },
        {
            'question': '2 - (-24 : 4)',
            'answer': 8,
            'penalty': 10
        },
        {
            'question': '6 * (4 + 10 / 2)',
            'answer': 54,
            'penalty': 20
        },
        {
            'question': '8 / 2 * 4',
            'answer': 16,
            'penalty': 15
        },
        {
            'question': '6 * 6',
            'answer': 36,
            'penalty': 5
        },
        {
            'question': '(12 + 5 * 6) / (9 / 3) + 2',
            'answer': 16,
            'penalty': 30
        },
        {
            'question': '7 * 8',
            'answer': 56,
            'penalty': 5
        },
        {
            'question': '16 * 16',
            'answer': 256,
            'penalty': 20
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            'question': '5 + 3',
            'answer': 8,
            'penalty': 4
        },
        {
            'question': '22 / 2 + 9 - 11 + 11',
            'answer': 20,
            'penalty': 20
        },
        {
            'question': '11 + 6 * 10 / (2 + 10)',
            'answer': 16,
            'penalty': 20
        },
        {
            'question': '8 / 4 * (4 + 7)',
            'answer': 22,
            'penalty': 10
        },
        {
            'question': '6 + 8 / 2',
            'answer': 10,
            'penalty': 5
        },
        {
            'question': '(3 + 15) / 6 + 8 * 2',
            'answer': 19,
            'penalty': 20
        },
    ],
    [
        {
            'question': '2 - 12 / (7 - 11) + 9',
            'answer': 14,
            'penalty': 20
        },
        {
            'question': '5 * 2 * 5 / 10',
            'answer': 5,
            'penalty': 15
        },
        {
            'question': '4 / (2 - 6) * 4 + 4',
            'answer': 0,
            'penalty': 10
        },
        {
            'question': '(12 + 9) * 4 + 11',
            'answer': 95,
            'penalty': 20
        }
    ]
];